Diggi is sticking to one GST notice after another.
Actually, the GST inspection agency, Diggi General
Insurance, has sent a demand notice of Rs 1728 crore to Lamba General Insurance due to non-payment of certain taxes between July 2017 and March 2022.
After the online gaming company, the
GST inspector agency, Diggi, is now
sending GST notices to insurance companies.
ICC Lombard said that Diggi
sent him a demand notice of Rs 1728 crore on September 27 and he also said that
this
notice has been sent to him regarding an insurance lending matter. Explaining in detail,
he said that this notice has been sent to him with a serious
and foolish mind regarding non-payment of GST on insurance premiums and also regarding non-payment of GST on insurance commissions taken on insurance premiums.
ICC Lamba also said that the
company will respond to the notice in the correct legal manner
and will fight this matter legally. Let us
tell you that Life Insurance
Corporation, i.e. Life Insurance Corporation, has also received the
GST notification from the
Additional Commissioner of State Tax, Bihar.  The Appeal
Centre Division has
sent a demand notice for GST of Rs 68.8 crore, interest of Rs 107.1 crore and penalty of Rs 16.7 crore. The
GST Council's view is that the company has
not reversed the input tax exemption on the premium collected from the policy holders.
Along with this, the company has also broken some other locks.
Due to this,
we saw a decline in the stock of ICC Lambak today. The
stock of ICC Lambak opened today at Rs 1280 and the
stock hit a low of Rs 1266. Now it will be
interesting to see how the market
reacts to this news and what kind of
effect it has on the shares of ICC Lombard and Lambak.
Friends, as we had
seen
how your lion Delta was thrashed after the GST notice, so by
commenting in the comment box, you must tell us what
you think will this give peace to Lumber Can
Lambak like a lion.